A Guide to the Photographs, Series 1011-1081 FA438
Rockefeller Archive Center
- John H. Knowles, 1049
  - Associates - Authors of "Doing Better and Feeling Worse", 18 (Box 37, Folder 374)
    Associates
  - Suffolk University, 1975; 19 (Box 37, Folder 375)
    Ceremonies, Graduations
  - Miscellaneous, 20 (Box 37, Folder 376)
    Graduations, Ceremonies, Medical Boards, Trustees, Meetings
  - John H. Knowles, Slides; Material is housed in an oversize box. (Box 37, Folder 377)
    Personal, Medical research, RF, Awards, Ceremonies, Retirement
- Conrad W. Anner, 1050
  An architect, Conrad W. Anner was born in Berlin, Germany, on December 20, 1889, the son of Edmund C. Anner. Conrad Anner graduated from the Division of Architecture of the Gewerbe Akademie, Chemnitz, Saxony, in 1909 and emigrated to the United States the same year. He married Caroline H. Foster in 1915; they had two children.
  Anner was first employed as a draughtsman by the Boston architectural firm Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge (1910-1917) and then by the Boston architect Thomas M. James (1917-1919). In 1919 he was hired by The Rockefeller Foundation as architectural draughtsman during the construction of Peking Union Medical College. Anner remained at PUMC until 1930 as supervisor of architectural work.
  Before returning to the United States, he was employed by St. Luke's International Hospital (Tokyo, Japan) to revise the plans of the hospital, and by the Chinese Government to design the National Institute for Physical Research in Shanghai and the National Meteorological Institute in Nanking.
  Following his return to the United States in 1931, Anner worked for the architectural firm Perry, Shaw & Hepburn as Superintendent of Construction at Colonial Williamsburg.
  Conrad W. Anner died in 1960.
  In addition to the material described in this finding aid, the Anner collection also contains slides picturing street scenes and landscapes.
  Anner, Conrad W.
  - Peking the Beautiful, Oversize book, 1 notebook in folder
    Peking
  - Thailand, Severe fading, silvering, mounted on acidic board; 1 (Box 38, Folder 378)
    Thailand, Buildings, landscapes, street scenes, temples, monuments
  - China 1, severe silvering, mounted on acidic board; 2 (Box 38, Folder 379)
    China, buildings, landscapes, monuments, temples, monuments, street scenes,
  - China, Severe silvering, mounted on acidic board; 3 (Box 38, Folder 380)
    China, buildings, landscapes, monuments, temples, street scenes,
  - China, Severe silvering, mounted on acid board; 4 (Box 38, Folder 381)
    China, temples, buildings, street scenes, monuments
  - China, Severe silvering, mounted on acidic board; 5 (Box 39, Folder 382)
    China, monuments, temples, buildings, construction, street scenes,
  - Peking Union Medical College, 6 (Box 39, Folder 383)
    architectural drawings
  - C. W. Anner Lantern Slides - China, Lantern Slides
    China, monuments, buildings, street scenes, landscapes, temples
  - C. W. Anner - China
    China, drawings, buildings
- Harry W. Frantz, 1051
  FA097 Harry W. Frantz photographs
  Frantz, Harry W.
- International Basic Economy Corporation, 1052
  For the International Basic Economic Corporation photographs please see Series 11 of:
  FA084 International Basic Economy Corporation records
  International Basic Economy Corporation
- Claude H. Barlow, 1053
  Claude H. Barlow (1876-1969) was born in Lyons, Michigan. In his youth he learned a variety of crafts and arts, including metal working, woodworking, and painting, which he later used in scientific research and illustration.
  Dr. Barlow attended the University of Michigan from 1899 to 1902 and received an M.D. degree from Northwestern in 1906.
  Joining the American Baptist Foreign Mission Society in 1908, Dr. Barlow began twenty years of service as a medical missionary in China. He was Customs Medical Officer for the Chinese Maritime Customs in Ningpo, for which his fees went to the hospital; he was also a surgeon and hospital superintendent in Shaosing. Dr. Barlow received a China Medical Board fellowship to study the human intestinal fluke, which led to a Sc.D. from Johns Hopkins in 1929.
  In 1929, Dr. Barlow joined the staff of the International Health Division and was sent to Egypt where he conducted hookworm and schistosomiasis campaigns and did basic snail research. In 1944 he infected himself with schistosomiasis in order to bring viable eggs to Johns Hopkins for study.
  With the outbreak of World War II, the foundation terminated its Egyptian program and Dr. Barlow joined the Egyptian Ministry of Health, where he remained until his retirement in 1951. In 1951, he conducted a snail survey for South Africa and then returned to the United States.
  Barlow, Claude H.
  - Claude H. Barlow, Many mounted on board; 1 (Box 40, Folder 393)
    Portraits, Candids, Jasper
  - China Fluke Study, Many wrinkled, creased, silvering; 2 (Box 40, Folder 394)
    Fluke, Biological studies, diseases
  - Egypt, some silvering; 3 (Box 40, Folder 395)
    landscapes, cities
  - Egypt - Anti-Schistosomiasis Project, Mounted on board; 4 (Box 41, Folder 396)
    Schistosomiasis, diseases, canals, drainage systems, public health
  - Egypt - Anti-Schistosomiasis Project, Two yellowed, mounted on board, captions on back; 5 (Box 41, Folder 397)
    Schistosomiasis, disease, public health, drainage systems, canals
  - Egypt - Anti-Schistosomiasis Project, Mounted on board, captions on back; 6 (Box 41, Folder 398)
    Schistosomiasis, disease, public health, indigenous peoples,
  - Egypt - Anti-Schistosomiasis Project, Mounted on board, captions on back; 7 (Box 41, Folder 399)
  - Egypt - Anti-Schistosomiasis Project, some curling, see also microfilm and lantern slides; 8 (Box 41, Folder 400)
    Schistosomiasis, snails, disease, public health
  - South African Snail Survey 1, Should separate contents, few curling; 9 (Box 41, Folder 401)
    Schistosomiasis, Public health, disease, indigenous peoples, landscapes, drainage systems
  - South African Snail Survey 2, Almost every image has a 120 mm neg., mounted on board, cations on back; 10 (Box 41, Folder 402)
    Snails, Public Health, indigenous peoples, landscapes
  - Claude H. Barlow, 11 (Box 41, Folder 403)
    Snails, Public Health, diseases, drainage systems, indigenous peoples, landscapes, sulphanation,
- General Education Board, 1054
  The General Education Board (GEB) was established in 1903 by John D. Rockefeller to aid education in the U.S. "without distinction of race, sex or creed." The program included grants for endowment and general budgetary support of colleges and universities, support for special programs, fellowship and scholarship assistance to state school systems at all levels, and development of social and economic resources as a route to improved educational systems. Major colleges and universities across the U.S., as well as many small institutions in every state, received aid from the Board. The emphasis, however, was on the South and the education of Blacks. Offices were established in Richmond, Virginia, and Baton Rouge, Louisiana, to give GEB agents closer contact with southern communities. The Board was especially active in promoting the public school movement in the early part of the twentieth century. After 1940, programs other than those for southern education were brought to a close; funds were nearly exhausted by the 1950s, and the last appropriation was made in 1964.
  General Education Board. (New York, N.Y.)
  - ALA 8 - Snow Hill Normal and Industrial Institute, 1930, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 404)
    Schools, students, teachers, Segregation
  - ALA 12 - Tuskegee Institute (Box 42, Folder 405)
    Tuskegee Institute, Schools, segregation, students, Classrooms, Laboratories, buildings, graduations
  - ALA 12 - Kowaliga School, 1909 (Box 42, Folder 406)
    Schools, Segregation, Alabama, Students, Buildings, Classrooms
  - ALA 42 - Talladega College (Box 42, Folder 407)
    Schools, segregation, graduations
  - ALA 146 - Birmingham - Southern College (Box 42, Folder 408)
    Schools, segregation
  - ALA 160.2 - Alabama Homemakers Clubs (Box 42, Folder 409)
    Students, Schools, Clubs
  - ALA 160 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - Negro, 1914-1916 (Box 42, Folder 410)
    Schools, segregation, faculty, students, buildings
  - ALA 163 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - White, 1914 (Box 42, Folder 411)
    Schools, students, faculty
  - ARK 44 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - Negro: Homemaker Clubs, 1915 (Box 42, Folder 412)
    Schools, segregation, students, faculty, clubs
  - ARK 45 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - White, 1915 (Box 42, Folder 413)
    Schools, Segregation
  - FLA 7 - State Agent for Secondary Education (Williston High School), 1919-1926 (Box 42, Folder 414)
    Schools, dedication ceremonies
  - FLA 39 - University of Florida, 1905-1954 (Box 42, Folder 415)
    Schools, construction
  - GA 10 - Spelman Seminary (Box 42, Folder 416)
  - GA 12 - Atlanta Library for Negro Institutions, 1931 (Box 42, Folder 417)
    Libraries, Schools, Segregation
  - GA 21 - Georgia Institute of Technology (Box 42, Folder 418)
    Schools, Segregation, Buildings
  - GA 39 - Agnes Scott College (Box 42, Folder 419)
    Schools, buildings, Segregation
  - GA 80 - Atlanta University, 1933 (Box 42, Folder 420)
  - GA 26 - Central High School, 1902 (Box 42, Folder 421)
  - GA 227 - Emory University (Box 43, Folder 422)
    Schools, buildings, segregation
  - GA 268 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - Negro (Box 43, Folder 423)
  - KY 6 - Berea College (Box 43, Folder 424)
    Schools, Buildings, Segregation
  - KY 20 - Kentucky State College (Box 43, Folder 425)
    Schools, Segregation, Students
  - KY 74 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - Negro, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 426)
  - LA 66 - Dillard University (Box 43, Folder 427)
    Schools, students, segregation, classrooms, plays
  - MISS 58 - Piney Woods School, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 428)
  - MISS 69 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - Negro, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 429)
  - LA 1 - Tulane University (Box 43, Folder 430)
    Schools, Buildings
  - NC 8 - Livingstone College, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 431)
    Schools, segregation, students
  - NC 81 - University of North Carolina (Box 43, Folder 432)
    Children, Schools, public health, segregation
  - NC 103 - North Carolina College of Agriculture and Engineering (Box 43, Folder 433)
    Students, Schools, laboratories
  - NC 236 - Supervisor for Rural Schools - Negro, 1915-1917 (Box 43, Folder 434)
    Schools, clubs, segregation, Buildings, students, faculty
  - NC 239 - Bennett College (Box 43, Folder 435)
    Schools, children, students, classrooms, medical exams, segregation
  - SC 3 - Vorrhees School and Junior College (Box 43, Folder 436)
    Schools, segregation, buildings
  - SC 11 - Penn Normal, Industrial and Agricultural School (Box 43, Folder 437)
  - SC 63 - Sumter Public School (Box 43, Folder 438)
    Schools, buildings, segregation, faculty
  - SC 103 - Clemson Agricultural College - rural education program (Box 43, Folder 439)
    Schools, segregation, faculty, staff, groups
  - SC 124a - Supervisor of Rural Schools - Negro (Box 43, Folder 440)
  - TENN 2a - Meharry Medical College (Box 43, Folder 441)
    Schools, Segregation, medical exams
  - TENN 12 - Fisk University (Box 43, Folder 442)
    Schools, segregation, children, classrooms
  - TENN 12.4 - Fisk University Summer School - Curriculum Laboratory for Negro Teachers (Box 43, Folder 443)
  - TENN 57 - George Peabody College for Teachers (Box 43, Folder 444)
    Schools, segregation, faculty
  - TENN 58 - Vanderbilt University (Box 43, Folder 445)
  - TENN 126 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - Negro - Homemakers Clubs, 1915-1916 (Box 43, Folder 446)
    Schools, segregation, buildings, clubs
  - TENN 126.1 - County Training Schools, 1915-1919 (Box 43, Folder 447)
    Schools, segregation, buildings, classrooms, faculty, students
  - TEX 22 - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas (Box 43, Folder 448)
    Schools, segregation, agriculture
  - TEX 11 - Huston - Tillotson College, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 449)
    Schools, segregation, faculty, students
  - TEX 27 - Bishop College, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 450)
  - TEX 93 - County Training School, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 451)
  - TEX 94 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - Negro (Box 43, Folder 452)
    Schools, Segregation, buildiings
  - VA 38 - Hampton Institute (Box 44, Folder 453)
    Schools, segregation, vocational training, classrooms, students
  - VA 38.1 - Hampton Institute - Summer School, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 454)
    Schools, classrooms, students, segregation
  - VA 38.1 - Hampton Institute - Summer School, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 455)
    Schools, segregation, faculty, students, children
  - VA 83 - University of Virginia (Box 44, Folder 456)
    Schools, segregation, faculty, students, classrooms
  - VA 83.1 - University of Virginia - Mountain Lake Biological Station (Box 44, Folder 457)
    Schools, segregation, classrooms, faculty, students
  - VA 119 - Virginia State College (for Negros) (Box 44, Folder 458)
    Schools, segregation, plays, graduations
  - VA 167 - Supervisor for Rural Schools - Negro, 1916, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 459)
    Schools, segregation, buildings, ceremonies
  - VA 170 - Supervisor of Rural Schools - White, 1915 (Box 44, Folder 460)
  - W. VA 20 - Life Planning Institute, 1929-1932, 1935 (Box 44, Folder 461)
    Schools, clubs, faculty, students
  - 193 - Conference of State superintendents and Agents for Negro Rural Schools, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 462)
    Schools, Segregation, Superentendants
  - 334 - Boy Scouts of America (Box 44, Folder 463)
    Segregation, Clubs, children
  - 374 - Southern Education Foundation (Box 44, Folder 464)
  - 375.1 - Institute of Jeanes Teachers (Box 44, Folder 465)
    Groups, schools, segregation
    Separated Materials
    Moved to Oversize.
  - 405 - Conference of College Treasurers (Box 44, Folder 466)
    Schools, segregation, conferences
  - 574 - Tarrytown School Survey, 1919-1921 (Box 44, Folder 467)
  - 594 - Survey of Science Teaching in Negro Schools, 1921-1924 (Box 44, Folder 468)
    Schools, segregation, students, classrooms
  - 595 - Critic Teachers, 1920 (Box 44, Folder 469)
    Groups, Schools, segregation
  - 597.1 - Model Rural School (Box 44, Folder 470)
    Schools, buildings
  - 600 - U. S. Department of Agriculture, 1938-1953 (Box 44, Folder 471)
    Agriculture, Farming, migratory labor
  - 600 - Conference to Outline Contributions of Extension Methods, 1944 September 19-22 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    Conferences, Schools
  - 600 - Purdue University - Farm Work Simplification Study (Box 44, Folder 473)
    Agriculture, farming, Schools
  - 628 - National Urban League, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 474)
    Schools
  - 632.11 - Progressive Education Association - Commission on Indian Education (Box 44, Folder 475)
    Schools, segregation, painting
  - 637 - Phelps Stokes Fund, 1918-1960 (Box 44, Folder 476)
    Segregation, construction, Classrooms, groups
  - 637.1 - Phelps Stokes Fund - Educational Survey of Africa, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 477)
    Schools, segregation, groups, construction
  - 648 - County Training Schools, 1915-1919 (Box 44, Folder 478)
  - 685 - Winchester Survey (Box 44, Folder 479)
  - 717- Humanities Conference, 1926 (Box 45, Folder 480)
    Groups, Schools, conferences
  - 724 - Carolina Art Association (Box 45, Folder 481)
    Schools, students, children, classrooms
  - 724 - Cleveland Museum of Art (Box 45, Folder 482)
    Schools, children, drawings, art
  - 724 - Conference on the Place of Industrial Art in General Education, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 483)
    Art exhibitions
  - 735 - Agricultural and Mechanical College for Negros, 1930-1931 (Box 45, Folder 484)
  - 725 - Flood Relief, 1927 (Box 45, Folder 485)
    natural disasters, towns, buildings
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1936-1937 (Box 45, Folder 486)
    Schools, agriculture, children, classrooms
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 487)
    Schools, classrooms, students, advertisements
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 488)
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 489)
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 490)
    Schools, segregation, faculty, students, classrooms, agriculture, plays, medical exams, children
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 491)
    Schools, segregation, agriculture, farming, classrooms, students, faculty
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 492)
    Schools, segregation, farming, classrooms, students
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 493)
    Schools, medical exams, military, students, faculty, segregation, children
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 494)
    Schools, farming, agriculture, faculty
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 495)
    Schools, segregation, medical exams, faculty
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 496)
    Schools, segregation, agriculture, migrant labor, children, medical exams
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 497)
    Schools, planning, construction, students, faculty, agriculture, children, medical exams
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 498)
    Schools, segregation, buildings, classrooms, students
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 499)
    Schools, segregation, classrooms, students, faculty
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 500)
  - 849 - Annual Report, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 501)
  - 849 - Review and Final Report, 1902-1964 (Box 46, Folder 502)
    Schools, faculty
  - 940 - American Council on Eductaion - Unemployed Youth (Box 46, Folder 503)
    Schools, art, trade skills, students
  - 950 - Alabama State Department of Education - Calhoun Public School for Negros, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 504)
  - 950 - Allen White High School (Box 46, Folder 505)
    Schools, segregation, construction
  - 950 - Associated Negro Press, 1931-1948 (Box 46, Folder 506)
    Segregation, Agriculture, Farming, children, medical exams
  - 950 - Atlanta University - Conference on Development of a school of Library Science, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 507)
    Schools, libraries, conferences
  - 950 - Baylor University - Drama (Box 46, Folder 508)
    Schools, plays, television
  - 950 - Bishop College - Community Workshop - Department of Homemaking Education (Box 46, Folder 509)
    Schools, segregation, construction, medical exams, children, classrooms, students
  - 950 - Booker T. Washington Birthplace Memorial (Box 46, Folder 510)
    Memorials
  - 950 - Brick Rural Life School (Box 46, Folder 511)
  - 950 - Dillard University - Departments of Art and Homemaking (Box 46, Folder 512)
    Schools, students, buildings, agriculture
  - 950 - Greenville County Coucil for Community Development, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 513)
    Schools, segregation, faculty, students, children, classrooms
  - 950 - Howard University - Family Life Workshop, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 514)
    Groups, schools, faculty
  - 950 - Interdenominational Theological Center - Atlanta, Georgia, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 515)
    Schools, religions
  - 950 - Karamu House - Theatre, 1940-1953 (Box 46, Folder 516)
    Schools, models
  - 950 - Louisiana Negro Normal and Industrial Institute - Workshop, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 517)
    Schools, segregation, faculty, students, children, classrooms, agriculture, farming, plays
  - 950 - Mississippi State College (Box 46, Folder 518)
  - 950 - Mississippi State College - Agricultural Experiment Station - Research (Box 46, Folder 519)
  - 950 - Nashville University Center (Box 46, Folder 520)
    Schools, faculty, ceremonies
  - 950 - National Council of Chief State School Officers (Box 46, Folder 521)
    Conferences, groups
  - 950 - Richmond University Center (Box 46, Folder 522)
  - 950 - Scarritt College for Christian Workers - Rural Training Center (Box 46, Folder 523)
  - 950 - Seminar on College Accounting, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 524)
  - 950 - Mississippi - Survey of Art Education, 1947-1949 (Box 47, Folder 525)
    Art, exhibitions.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 450, Folder 4763
  - 950 - Nashville School of Social Work (Box 47, Folder 526)
    Schools, trustees.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 456, Folders 4844-4846
  - 950 - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools - Conference in Elementary Education, 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 527)
    Schools, faculty, groups.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 469, Folder 5002
  - 950 - Southwestern Land Tenure Research Committee, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 528)
    Groups, conferences.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 477, Folders 5081-5084
  - 950 - Tuskegee Institute - Development Program - School of Veterinary Medicine (Box 47, Folder 529)
    Schools, segregation, animals, laboratories, classrooms, buildings, construction.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 487, Folders 5194-5195
  - 950 - Tuskegee Institute - Rural Life (Box 47, Folder 530)
    Schools, segregation, children, students, classrooms, teachers, recreation.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 489, Folders 5208-5209
  - 950 - Tuskegee Institute - Study of Rural Housing, 1937-1939 (Box 47, Folder 531)
    Houses, construction, communities, towns.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 490, Folder 5229
  - 950 - University of Georgia - Art Department, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 532)
    Schools, art exhibits.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 498, Folders 5310-5312 and Box 499, Folders 5313-5317
  - 950 - University of Louisville - Southern Police Institute (Box 47, Folder 533)
    Lectures, groups, conferences, schools.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 502, Folders 5358-5360 and Box 503, Folders 5361-5366
  - 950 - University of Mississippi - Library (Box 47, Folder 534)
    Schools, libraries, students.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 504, Folder 5375
  - 950 - University of North Carolina - Institute of Statistics (Box 47, Folder 535)
    Groups, schools.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 508, Folder 5421
  - 950 - Vanderbilt University - Institute of Research and Training in the Social Sciences (Box 47, Folder 536)
    Schools, students, faculty.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 521, Folders 5561-5562
  - 950 - Virginia State College for Negroes - Summer School for Ministers, 1944-1949 (Box 47, Folder 537)
    Schools, groups, segregation.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 524, Folder 5595
  - 950 - Virginia Union University - Library Building, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 538)
    Schools, libraries, buildings, art exhibits.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 526, Folders 5617-5622
  - 950 - West Virginia University - Conference, 1940-1941 (Box 47, Folder 539)
    Farming, field trips, groups.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 527, Folder 5636
  - 950.1 - Duke University - Forestry (Box 47, Folder 540)
    Schools, forestry.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 530, Folder 5672
  - 950.1 - "Forestry in the South", 1940 (Box 47, Folder 541)
    Forestry, landscape, agriculture, farming.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 530, Folders 5678-5680
  - 950.2 - Duke University - Marine Laboratory, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 542)
    Buildings, laboratories, marine sciences.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 532, Folder 5706
  - 950.3 - Auburn Research Foundation, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 543)
    Nutrition, machinery, food processor.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 535, Folder 5726
  - 950.3 - Virginia State Nutrition Committee (Box 47, Folder 544)
    Parents, children, nutrition.
    Removed from GEB, Series 1.3, Box 539, Folders 5776-5777
  - 950.3 - Mississippi State Department of Education - Coordinated School Health and Nutrition Services (Box 47, Folder 545)
    Schools, segregation, children, faculty.
    Removed from GEB, Series, 1.3, Box 541, Folders 5802-5805
  - 950.4 - North Carolina College for Negroes - Health Education (Box 47, Folder 546)